A Wipro Anshu ji, your opinion is that the
stock is trying to move a bit before the results,
however there is still a lot of scope,
should one buy or wait for the results, do
whatever you want to do after that
sir, it is better to wait for the results
because there are two problems, first the result is
looming large, second the 50
day moving average is getting rejected again and again since the last five sessions,
in the range of 208 20850, then a
breakout of at least 210 will be required, in that case the stock
can stretch to ₹219.40
and if it crosses that then it will go up
to ₹226 to fill the gap, but the results are in front and the 50
day moving average is getting rejected again and again, so
I will wait for 210 to come out.
After that I will try to create a long position.
So wait for 210 to come out.  Then you
can take a long position.
Look, wait a little for 210 to come out.
After that you have to create a position
and this distance of ₹210 is only ₹2 left,
almost
in banking I would like to take an opinion on SBI share,
this share went below ₹1000,
falling from ₹150 and after that the
recovery process has started again.
Kunal ji, will SBI be able to achieve its old levels
?
How much potential do you see in this expiry
?   It is a
bit difficult to say at this expiry.
But yes, I feel like I think the
stock is regaining its momentum slowly and steadily.
You know if we
see in the last four days there was not
such a big jump or such a big rally in PSU banking stocks as
we saw last year you know in the second half of 2025,
many PSU banking names SBI
PNB, NCR Bank, Bank of Baroda Assets, all of them had
a good move of around you know 30%.
After that it seems
that the start is a bit slow for SBI.
But I believe that I think as soon as
confidence comes in Bank Nifty,
confidence comes in the market, then
these PSU banking stocks can perform very well.
So, instead of
taking it as a short term trade, it should be
seen from the point of view of positional trade.  SBI and
Canara Bank and all these stocks.  So it
looks attractive from the current level.
SBI is trading around 180.  But I
believe that perhaps this will go into a slow gradual and
steady up trend.  However, rather than
momentum up trend.
Ok.  Ok.  This also happened with SBI.
We saw a big rise in A New India Insurance
in Monday's session
but today there is profit taking in it.
And the problem with this is that these mean big
moves do happen but somewhere the range
is defined.  After reaching around ₹200,
some fatigue always starts setting in and
we have seen this pattern in the last one and a half, two-three years.
Lakshmikant ji, what should be your opinion regarding New India Assurance
?  Buy on dip or stay away.
No, according to me, buy on dip should be done only.  The
strong hurdle is around 175 180.
Ah, on Monday's session, a
spike was taken here once but again
profit booking is seen here,
so I think if it
retraces to a lower level, around 160, in the
range of 160 to 162, then there
can be an opportunity for buying. Ah, the
stop loss at that time will be 154
and if there is a pullback move from here, then
again we will be able
to see the levels of 180 to 185 here.